<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://alpharoast.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 02:04:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://alpharoast.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Ad Network Alliance</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/netflix-ad-network-alliance-9ce2aeb13cc1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 02:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/netflix-ad-network-alliance-9ce2aeb13cc1/</guid>
      <description>Every quarter a new analyst predicts the impending launch of ads on Netflix, typically followed up with other analysts reminding them that Netflix already has ads — native ads. Netflix has been quietly growing their product integration business for years. I wouldn’t be surprised if they started breaking out revenue shortly to assure Wall Street that they have diversified revenue.
What’s more, while Netflix is incredibly stingy with data, I’m sure they’re already sharing significant deidentified/aggregated data with the massive agencies buying native integration in their shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is PrEP?</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/what-is-prep-f96b34eb4ae9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 14:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/what-is-prep-f96b34eb4ae9/</guid>
      <description>PrEP–Pre-exposure Prophylaxis–commonly refers to drugs taken before exposure to prevent HIV infections. In France, they’ve begun trials for a proactive medication regimen to prevent syphilis; they’re also referring to it as PrEP. This raises an important question, if PrEP can prevent syphilis and HIV, but are different protocols, what then is PrEP?
Scientific advances have started to free a generation of gay men from the shackles of the historic trauma of the AIDS Crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Once a gay bar, America has devolved into a Chili’s</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/once-a-gay-bar-america-has-devolved-into-a-chilis-491a3cc068b7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 14:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/once-a-gay-bar-america-has-devolved-into-a-chilis-491a3cc068b7/</guid>
      <description>I imagine many of you have never entered a gay bar; that’s okay! To be frank, my experiences in gay bars have all occurred in the Chili’s Era. My nostalgia of gay bars is of an idyllic time I never witnessed, but rather has been regaled to me by men who survived police beatings and the AIDS crisis, by men who were told they could never marry or be open at work for fear of harassment and termination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design, de Blasio, Debate, and Debauchery</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/design-de-blasio-debate-and-debauchery-914948087b46/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 18:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/design-de-blasio-debate-and-debauchery-914948087b46/</guid>
      <description>Maybe you enjoyed your podcasts on a stroll through the park during our unseasonably warm weekend last week. This week, I suggest bundling up and hunkering down to our playlist. Sorry this is coming out a little late. One member of the team got a little too obsessed with Super Mario Odyssey this week… Not going to say who.
The meandering playlist actually starts with a video, but it’s in partnership with one of our favorite programs — 99% Invisible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colony collapse, crosswords, cohabitation, and college athletes</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/colony-collapse-crosswords-cohabitation-and-college-athletes-eb3bbcfb8424/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 18:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/colony-collapse-crosswords-cohabitation-and-college-athletes-eb3bbcfb8424/</guid>
      <description>How ‘bout this weather! If you’re enjoying the unseasonably warm rays in early November with a stroll through Central Park, maybe listen to one of these podcasts. No, we’re not going to bring you down with climate podcasts, but if you want to hear about the US government’s most comprehensive study ever, check out this brief report from NPR.
Back to your stroll through the park, maybe check out a podcast about the alarming decline of bee populations worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spooky Stories and Lessons Learned</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/spooky-stories-and-lessons-learned-23a2696f654d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 18:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/spooky-stories-and-lessons-learned-23a2696f654d/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Week 8. We got quite a few positive responses after changing up last week’s newsletter format and the open rate was 2x higher, so we’re going to continue that and see how it goes! Given it’s Halloween weekend, we found a few spooky podcasts and mixed in some of our other favorite episodes this week.
We also saw 2 Dope Queens live on Monday as part of their filming for their HBO special.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindhunter, Medicine, Moonshots &amp; Mantzoukas</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/mindhunter-medicine-moonshots-mantzoukas-568c0bedf086/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 18:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/mindhunter-medicine-moonshots-mantzoukas-568c0bedf086/</guid>
      <description>This week is a little different. We’ll be honest, we needed to change up our podcast diet. A bout of sickness and busy work schedule made it a little more difficult than usual to scour the podcast archives, so we turned to our comfort food, our staples, our favorites. We selected six podcasts we really enjoyed so that maybe you can enjoy them this weekend, too!
Have you liked or subscribed to any of the podcasts we’ve recommended?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assistance, Astrophysics, Action, and Adaptations</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/assistance-astrophysics-action-and-adaptations-aa13c06408fa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 18:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/assistance-astrophysics-action-and-adaptations-aa13c06408fa/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Week 6. Given the news has been a bit hard on all of us for some time, we tried to pick out some more uplifting topics. We also decided to start experimenting with a Facebook group. It’s open and we’d love to invite all of you to join. We’ll start up some discussions this weekend.
This week, we open with a discussion about the Red Cross and charitable giving in general; Mic closes the topic on a hopeful note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Riots, Rifles, Rock &amp; Roll, and a Writer</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/riots-rifles-rock-roll-and-a-writer-b89aa6da1c3c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 17:58:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/riots-rifles-rock-roll-and-a-writer-b89aa6da1c3c/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Week 5. It’s been trying to comb through audio about heavy events, but we think we’ve found some great perspectives. We’re working on some processes to streamline the discovery of audio, but wanted to give a shout out to the team at Audiosear.ch as they’ve become invaluable to our initial discovery. If you have any strategies for finding new shows or topical episodes, please reach out to us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assembly, AIDS, Activism, and Anthologies</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/assembly-aids-activism-and-anthologies-e866447e2553/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 17:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/assembly-aids-activism-and-anthologies-e866447e2553/</guid>
      <description>Week four and triple-digit subscribers! This passion project takes tens of hours a week (not that we’re not enjoying listening to tons of different stories), but it makes it all the more worth it knowing there’s a few people out there enjoying it with us.
On the last week of September, we start with an examination of the Senate, provide color around HIV after some exciting announcements, and consider where taking a knee fits in history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exodus, Earthquakes, Emmys, and Equifax</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/exodus-earthquakes-emmys-and-equifax-89a24d1b4ca7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 17:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/exodus-earthquakes-emmys-and-equifax-89a24d1b4ca7/</guid>
      <description>Bird &amp;amp; Candy here, back after searching the annals to discover interesting audio for your weekend. This week we focused on the humanitarian crisis in Myanmar, geological disasters in Mexico, diversity at the Emmys, and the ongoing consumer credit fiasco that is Equifax.
We pulled together voices from across the world, from New Zealand (twice) to Wall Street to the UK, relying heavily on public media. It’s a reminder of how vital non-profit driven journalism is to recording and understanding our collective history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hermits, Hacking, Hollywood, and Her</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/hermits-hacking-hollywood-and-her-e598d6805a83/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 17:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/hermits-hacking-hollywood-and-her-e598d6805a83/</guid>
      <description>Holy hell, readers, what a week! We were feeling so energized having sent our first newsletter last Friday that we really went deep this week on podcasts. We decided to expand the slate of shows covered, so let us know what you think compared to last week!
The world is an uncertain place, but we found some pretty interesting stuff for you to devour this weekend. First, we did a deep dive on the Hermit Kingdom, North Korea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diana, Disasters, and Don Jr.</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/diana-disasters-and-don-jr-979cd05333c7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 17:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/diana-disasters-and-don-jr-979cd05333c7/</guid>
      <description>We’re scouring the interwebs for podcasts tangential to the news to give you more color about what’s happening in this crazy world of ours.
This week, we take a look back at Princess Diana, Hurricane Katrina, and Watergate. We also threw in a fun podcast from one of our absolutely favorite shows, Reply All. Make sure to like, rate, and share these podcasts as it really helps the producers.
If you’re able, please take a moment and donate to Direct Relief, a charity to “improve the health and lives of people affected by poverty or emergency situations by mobilizing and providing essential medical resources needed for their care”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency, Urban Development, and Square</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/cryptocurrency-urban-development-and-square-783ada5d3c10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 14:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/cryptocurrency-urban-development-and-square-783ada5d3c10/</guid>
      <description>16 DECEMBER 2013
Those three things seem really unrelated, but stick with me for a few minutes and maybe I can make some sense of them. There’s definite holes in my ideas, but it’s a start.
Cryptocurrency… What? Think Bitcoin.
If you haven’t heard of Bitcoin by now I’m amazed. Regardless, it’s actually not as complex of a concept as pundits would make you believe.
Bitcoin is a ledger. It’s distributed and uses algorithms to verify transactions, eliminating the need for a central bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase and E-Commerce</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/coinbase-and-e-commerce-f6092ab4dc33/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 14:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/coinbase-and-e-commerce-f6092ab4dc33/</guid>
      <description>I’ve had this blog sitting unfinished for quite some time. Today’s annoucement that Balanced and Coinbase are partnering spurred me to wrap it up.
Shtick to Serious Raise your hand if you’re tired of seeing PR headlines reading “X is now accepting Bitcoin!”. If you’re not tired because it’s a lame marketing ploy you’re definitely tired because you have no idea what this Bitcoin thing is and where to get it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Traveling Bard</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/the-traveling-bard-e890a3861b99/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 19:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/the-traveling-bard-e890a3861b99/</guid>
      <description>Storytellers need to meet their audiences where they spend their time
The Bard (ca. 1817), by John Martin
Major Media companies aren’t having the best decade. A one-two punch from Google and Facebook has flattened onsite traffic and ad revenue, and the digital “platforms” they invested in are no longer very valuable.
When selling ads, audience data and size are pretty important, and digital platforms like Facebook, Snapchat, and YouTube have audience in troves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tesla: The Next Tech Giant?</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/tesla-the-next-tech-giant-a740ac200043/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 15:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/tesla-the-next-tech-giant-a740ac200043/</guid>
      <description>The growth of edge computing favors this automotive upstart
Twitter’s Fabric sold to Google, and yesterday Facebook’s Parse shut down. The social upstarts that sought to dethrone computing superpowers by democratizing development tools have largely failed. No, it’s a bookstore that managed to assail the previous moats built by Oracle, Microsoft, and Google out of millions of servers.
It seems the dominant tech platform of our time is turning over at an ever increasing pace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Would love to see you expand the pod to include Flash Briefings and/or Spoken Editions.</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/would-love-to-see-you-expand-the-pod-to-include-flash-briefings-and-or-spoken-editions-89c0c9091971/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 20:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/would-love-to-see-you-expand-the-pod-to-include-flash-briefings-and-or-spoken-editions-89c0c9091971/</guid>
      <description>Would love to see you expand the pod to include Flash Briefings and/or Spoken Editions. Happy to assist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Chatbots, Now What?</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/so-chatbots-now-what-6347a6c42d14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 20:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/so-chatbots-now-what-6347a6c42d14/</guid>
      <description>The renaissance of chat seems to be sputtering
Stop me if you’ve heard this before:
 Chatbots are taking over the world!
 I could insert graphs showing messenger applications overtaking social media applications, graphs showing the death of apps, or even better graphs of the meteoric rise of FB Messenger Bots created over the past few months. And yet, while text-based bots are experiencing a rebirth from their SmarterChild days, we should start exploring why text-based UX has made a resurgence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Thoughts on Medium</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/quick-thoughts-on-medium-27eb4a852554/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 18:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/quick-thoughts-on-medium-27eb4a852554/</guid>
      <description>Last week, Evan Williams wrote about building a new business model for publishing, and the human cost of changing course. Undoubtedly, Medium has loads of cash and talent left that will continually delight us. However, I have persisting, serious doubts in a text-based media world.
Listen along as I read my words! Pardon the awful sound quality.
Would you click on any of these?
The problems inherent to the digital media space are obvious: click-bait headlines, auto-play video, poor ad experiences, obnoxious content recommendation widgets, the list goes on and on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I just need to write something</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/i-just-need-to-write-something-45ddeb01e468/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 18:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/i-just-need-to-write-something-45ddeb01e468/</guid>
      <description>The media must shoulder blame for this election. We failed at our jobs, spectacularly. I want to write a post about the shortsighted strategy of pursuing ad views, about prioritizing clicks over thoughtful consumption, about chasing fads and virality. I could write that post and feel personally vindicated for 15 minutes, but the harder conversation to be had, specifically in the news/journalism industry, is asking what our purpose is.
In a new world where users have turned to their friends’ recommendations on Facebook, where algorithms decide what we see and consume, are we still adding value by writing another article with a catchy headline?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-Debate Podcast Binging</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/post-debate-podcast-binging-65f1d0ab7b6c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 01:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/post-debate-podcast-binging-65f1d0ab7b6c/</guid>
      <description>Get hot takes from some great pundits
Last night was depressing. As difficult as that “debate” was to watch, voting and education are essential to our democracy. This election cycle, we’re lucky to have some awesome podcasts to keep us up to date and help breakdown some of the more esoteric moments.
Today, I’ve thrown on my headphones and powered through some of these great podcasts and will run you through some of my favorites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unsure how to confront news like this:</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/unsure-how-to-confront-news-like-this-fd5e0b61e95a/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 18:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/unsure-how-to-confront-news-like-this-fd5e0b61e95a/</guid>
      <description>Unsure how to confront news like this:
Gay Soccer Ref in Spain Getting Death Threats from Fans After Coming Out | VICE Sports
_Jesus Tomillero has endured slurs and is now getting death threats since coming out as gay._sports.vice.com
Super disappointing. I’d like to meet these “fans” in person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter is as close to perfect a second screen TV app as you can get, and they have no…</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/twitter-is-as-close-to-perfect-a-second-screen-tv-app-as-you-can-get-and-they-have-no-phone-b4b80abba2ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 20:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/twitter-is-as-close-to-perfect-a-second-screen-tv-app-as-you-can-get-and-they-have-no-phone-b4b80abba2ab/</guid>
      <description>Twitter is as close to perfect a second screen TV app as you can get, and they have no phone-experience integration in their OTT app. Absolutely crazy product miss IMO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Talk About Sex</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/lets-talk-about-sex-bbd245738662/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 17:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/lets-talk-about-sex-bbd245738662/</guid>
      <description>Gimlet Media’s Science Vs is an amazing podcast, full stop. Go listen right now.
Wendy Zuckerman and her kick-ass team of Kaitlyn Sawrey and Heather Rogers have been flawless in their production of Science Vs. This week does not disappoint as they explore the G-spot. I don’t know if this episode will garner as many downloads as Reply All’s LSD Microdosing episode, but read this description and tell me you aren’t going to listen:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comments Be Damned</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/comments-be-damned-e60a959074d2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 15:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/comments-be-damned-e60a959074d2/</guid>
      <description>Two weeks ago, NPR announced that they will be removing comments from their domain, and instead rely on third-party social platforms to engage with their audience.
Stolen from Syracuse.com
This continues a trend of major media creators abandoning on-site discussions and further ceding audience engagement to Facebook (and sometimes Twitter). Much of the discussion is around an issue with moderation and the abysmal rate of interaction. Working at AOL.com, I can attest to the useless vitriol that inhabits so many commenting platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brian Fitzsimmons your Nets under fire!</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/brian-fitzsimmons-your-nets-under-fire-27d8a7092b54/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 00:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/brian-fitzsimmons-your-nets-under-fire-27d8a7092b54/</guid>
      <description>Brian Fitzsimmons your Nets under fire!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey Apple, Buy App.net. Love, Brad</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/hey-apple-buy-app-net-love-brad-a84b36ef34e8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 20:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/hey-apple-buy-app-net-love-brad-a84b36ef34e8/</guid>
      <description>Following my thoughts that Twitter should buy Kik to bolster their pre-IPO offerings, I figured I’d swing for the fences on another acquisition.
Who should Apple really buy? Dropbox — like yesterday. Unfortunately, I don’t think Tim Cook et al. will make a purchase like that and admit their cloud services are a mess. It’s no secret Apple has lost some of their mojo since the passing of Steve Jobs. But I think they’ve also grown their own set of issues when they built the simplest phone OS to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Used To Be Psychic</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/i-used-to-be-psychic-ab3396582c84/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 20:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/i-used-to-be-psychic-ab3396582c84/</guid>
      <description>The other week I rented a car for the first time and it reminded me of my former 6th sense. You see, I used to be able to look into the future; I used to be psychic.
My parents, bless their hearts, were very good about taking us on vacations as children. We’d show up to the airport hours early in order to assuage my mother’s perpetual anxiety over missing our flight, and commence with incessant bickering and boredom that drove my parents to the very brink of insanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ear Tickling Goodness</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/ear-tickling-goodness-59000e36ca92/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 17:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/ear-tickling-goodness-59000e36ca92/</guid>
      <description>Happy Friday! Ready to get your ears tickled? Onto this week’s update:
I fucking love podcasts. Don’t believe me, well, I blogged about it because I’m a narcissist and figured you’d want to know. It can be tough to jump in, so here’s a quick list of new episodes you should check out this weekend.
Get that dirt off your shoulders The Watch — ‘Game of Thrones’ Finale, ‘The Night Of,’ and Jay Z’s New Single — 53:04</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Fucking Love Podcasts</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/i-fucking-love-podcasts-dd6c801919c7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 18:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/i-fucking-love-podcasts-dd6c801919c7/</guid>
      <description>And god damnit, you will too.
If you saw me on the subway this past winter, you wouldn’t have described me as looking happy. That’s probably true of 99.9% of people on the train. But we all know that .1% of the population that’s completely unhinged, happy to be jammed into a subway car that’s more akin to a sausage casing.
Except I’ve changed. I discovered podcasts. And if I happen to be listening to one of the many amazing comedy podcasts like Two Dope Queens, or my current personal favorite How Did This Get Made, it’s very likely I’ll be shamelessly cackling amongst the masses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Catharsis of Coming Out</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/the-catharsis-of-coming-out-fc18ceb72be8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 15:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/the-catharsis-of-coming-out-fc18ceb72be8/</guid>
      <description>Being comfortable with myself continues to be life changing.
In the wake of the Orlando murders, many of us have been left with unanswerable questions. I myself spent a considerable amount of time dissecting the layers of information; my preferred coping mechanisms are over-rationalization and intellectualization, hence this post.
Among many revelations over the last few days, it seems the murderer frequented the nightclub and had a profile on some gay dating apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An index bot that can recommend the best bot for your task?</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/an-index-bot-that-can-recommend-the-best-bot-for-your-task-6364a713c9b7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 21:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/an-index-bot-that-can-recommend-the-best-bot-for-your-task-6364a713c9b7/</guid>
      <description>An index bot that can recommend the best bot for your task?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter — Who would buy them?</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/twitter-who-would-buy-them-d30c068476cf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 19:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/twitter-who-would-buy-them-d30c068476cf/</guid>
      <description>I love the Stratechery blog and accompanying podcast, Exponent.fm. Lately (well actually for years) Ben Thompson has been critical of Twitter and it’s future.
I count myself as a former lover of Twitter’s product, but today can hardly be bothered to check it; that’s a bad [albeit anecdotal] sign. To save time reiterating all that Ben said, here’s a nice catchup from this week: How Facebook Squashed Twitter
A common debate I’ve read is who should buy Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovative Sports Media Strategy</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/innovative-sports-media-strategy-a5e967f26b62/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 22:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/innovative-sports-media-strategy-a5e967f26b62/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I wrote about how football dying could kill college athletics. Today I’m going to share part of an email describing a media strategy I suggested to a D2 school.
During my fairly unsuccessful job search in 2012, I decided to email an athletic director about starting a football program at his school as part of a comprehensive media strategy. My motivation was simple, it was the intersection of my two biggest passions: athletics and technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Better Spring Game</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/a-better-spring-game-3b94d6bf896b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 21:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/a-better-spring-game-3b94d6bf896b/</guid>
      <description>Have you played college football? If not, let me tell you a little secret: football practice in the Spring is the worst.
Seriously.
Fall camp is really brutal, but there’s an end goal. In Spring Ball your only goal is to be done with Spring Ball.
I’m heading back to my alma mater next weekend for our annual Spring Game and it dawned on me that this is a ridiculous event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freicoin and Square</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/freicoin-and-square-dfe54bf9e075/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 21:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/freicoin-and-square-dfe54bf9e075/</guid>
      <description>Freicoin is based on the concept of demurrage was first introduced by Silvio Gesell and implemented successfully in Wörgl, Austria. I think it could be used by Square to help drive urban development.
First things first, WTF is Freicoin?  Freicoin is a peer-to-peer (P2P) currency based on the accounting concept of a proof-of-work block chain used by Satoshi Nakamoto in the creation of Bitcoin. Unlike Bitcoin, Freicoin has a demurrage fee that ensures its circulation and bearers of the currency pay this fee automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wisdom from Dylan Meier</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/wisdom-from-dylan-meier-3eed61a01f70/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 21:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/wisdom-from-dylan-meier-3eed61a01f70/</guid>
      <description>Cleaning out my car this morning, I found a quote from Dylan that rang especially true with me.
Dylan would have been 30 years young last Friday. He was wise well beyond his years.
 I’m truly grateful to have the family I have. Seeing and being with them is what I value as love… unconventional love and an abundance of security, smiles, and memories; unforgettable memories.
  -DQM</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seeing Through The Fog</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/seeing-through-the-fog-860c1119daf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 21:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/seeing-through-the-fog-860c1119daf1/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been told many times that the process of coming out is cathartic. Yet since coming to terms with my sexuality, I found it arduous and unnecessary. At least that’s what I kept telling myself. So today, I’m putting it in writing and not looking back.
 I’m gay.
 I’m also an athlete. For years, I struggled to unite these two identities in my own mind. Not until after my professional athletic career came to an end did I allow myself to understand my sexuality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen and the Art of Quitting Football</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/zen-and-the-art-of-quitting-football-2d1166149141/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 21:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/zen-and-the-art-of-quitting-football-2d1166149141/</guid>
      <description>We have a choice — in everything we do — between creation and destruction, yin and yang.
 John Moffitt was shouting wisdom over the jazz ensamble playing at High Dive in Fremont Seattle, only a week after leaving rehab. With every club soda ordered, he left an overly generous tip.
 I hated the NFL; I hated football when I quit. I wanted to destroy everything about it, but in the end all I was destroying was myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Bingham (1970–2001)</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/mark-bingham-1970-2001-871c8f1a8e86/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 15:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/mark-bingham-1970-2001-871c8f1a8e86/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted at http://www.sffog.org/about
One of our brothers, Mark Bingham, was tragically taken from us on Tuesday, Sept. 11, 2001, during the terrorist attack on our nation. He was one of the 38 passengers on hijacked United Airlines flight 93 that crashed outside of Pittsburgh. Mark was 31 years old.
Mark epitomized what it means to be a Fog rugger, and we all learned a great deal from him. Aside from being a superb player, “Bear Trap” was a true gentleman and a generous friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hub and Spoke Publishing</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/hub-and-spoke-publishing-90058ec6246e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 00:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/hub-and-spoke-publishing-90058ec6246e/</guid>
      <description>To make things easy, I’m going to write about what I’m doing right now. Since I just started working at a fairly large publisher, it should be easy to write a few hundred words about some problems we (publishers) are facing.
The Original Internet
Since the rise and fall of AOL as the center of the internet, publishing has been in constant flux. One thing that’s remained fairly constant is publishers’ hosting content within their own domains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Coaching</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/on-coaching-5f9de431de71/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 22:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/on-coaching-5f9de431de71/</guid>
      <description>One of my alma maters isn’t performing too well in football these days. It’s difficult to watch, to say the least.
Numerous factors play into this of which I’m likely both ignorant of their existence and complexity so I’ll refrain from commenting on my former institution specifically. What I think I can speak on is the ineptitude in adapting coaching strategies to well studied management and motivation theories.
My own two cents is that coaches are generally evaluated on wins and losses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camp Techstars</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/camp-techstars-f2793099dbd6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/camp-techstars-f2793099dbd6/</guid>
      <description>Colorado Mountain Ranch, Gold Hill
On the way to summer camp my gut turned as nervous energy controlled my thoughts. Behind me I watched as my old friends and memories faded into the distance and only question marks ahead of me, down a long strange road. What would the other campers be like? Would I make any friends? Will I have to share a shower?
The next three months became a frenzy of crashing go karts, racing down water slides, drinking around campfires (or more commonly overly crowded tables), regretting drinking around campfires, biking over mountains, and innumerable other activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey Apple, Buy App.net. Love, Brad</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/hey-apple-buy-app-net-love-brad-22192bcb37b9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/hey-apple-buy-app-net-love-brad-22192bcb37b9/</guid>
      <description>Originally published on 17 April 2013
Following my thoughts that Twitter should buy Kik to bolster their pre-IPO offerings, I figured I’d swing for the fences on another acquisition.
Who should Apple really buy? Dropbox — like yesterday. Unfortunately, I don’t think Tim Cook et al. will make a purchase like that and admit their cloud services are a mess. It’s no secret Apple has lost some of their mojo since the passing of Steve Jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Buys Vizio</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/microsoft-buys-vizio-daa9ab1b1fbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/microsoft-buys-vizio-daa9ab1b1fbe/</guid>
      <description>Originally published on April 17, 2013.
I wrote this last Spring and never published it. I did buy a Chromebook and I still think Microsoft should buy Vizio but I think we’ll see Facebook buying XBox before long and then Microsoft will be gone. Enjoy:
I don’t want to write very long on this subject. I feel pretty confident with this prediction.
Okay, Microsoft probably won’t buy Vizio but Vizio will make Windows relevant in a fast approaching post PC market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey Twitter, Buy Kik. Love, Brad</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/hey-twitter-buy-kik-love-brad-1973c2537cda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/hey-twitter-buy-kik-love-brad-1973c2537cda/</guid>
      <description>Twitter is gearing up for an IPO. Folks are looking for some liquidity and Twitter is looking to diversify their revenue streams. After all, nobody wants to repeat that Facebook pre IPO roadshow where their lack of a mobile strategy nearly screwed everything up. Facebook has a great mobile strategy now and they nabbed a (seemingly non integrated) Instagram from under Twitter’s nose for a cool $1B.
So you’re Twitter, you’ve gone and acquired Vine which is doing great (unless you’re on Android that is), oh, and you’re working on some high level deals with broadcasters to include video in tweets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amicus’ First Biz Dev Hire? Yes Please</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/amicus-first-biz-dev-hire-yes-please-9cdea3393425/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/amicus-first-biz-dev-hire-yes-please-9cdea3393425/</guid>
      <description>Originally published on January 10, 2013.
Seth!
I thought about reaching out through a friend of a friend of a friend but the world wide web is more efficient than that. I wrote you this beautiful note so that you would hire me!
This job listing was on Hacker News! Woah I must be like 1 of 1000 applicants in the last hour so let’s make this interesting because lord knows you’re likely bored of cover letters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Time, I Biked To Omaha</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/this-one-time-i-biked-to-omaha-5baa50129e4f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/this-one-time-i-biked-to-omaha-5baa50129e4f/</guid>
      <description>We’re on the verge of a new year, the Mayans were wrong, and hopefully 2013 is full of more employment opportunities than 2012.
The Present I am unemployed, partially by choice, as I am one of those privileged white kids who gets to be mad at the world for not bending to his every whim and giving him what he wants. But also because I’ve been summarily denied from every job for which I have applied, some of which I’ve been qualified for, others not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Parcel Delivery</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/the-future-of-parcel-delivery-5d2405138158/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/the-future-of-parcel-delivery-5d2405138158/</guid>
      <description>Anybody who truly, truly knows me knows I really dislike the United States Postal Service. Mostly because I wrote the Postmaster General a long letter in high school on steps he could take to make the aging service more meaningful in our lives and potentially profitable. Someday I’ll get over being ignored but I’m not quite ready.
What gives me hope is talks of Amazon debuting a locker delivery service and BufferBox getting Y Combinator support to do similar things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Energy and Food — Fixing the Economy</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/energy-and-food-fixing-the-economy-35770f857079/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/energy-and-food-fixing-the-economy-35770f857079/</guid>
      <description>I’ve read some fantastic blogs on oil prices as of late that have inspired some bloggable thoughts of my own. For quite sometime I’ve thought that energy and food systems must be disrupted in order for significant societal progress to occur. Clearly fossil fuels are not an infinite solution and agricultural subsidies are some of the worst crimes against humanity and yet are no less commonplace in the US than air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Google Fiber Means For Public Education</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/what-google-fiber-means-for-public-education-624381e540a8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/what-google-fiber-means-for-public-education-624381e540a8/</guid>
      <description>This idea hit me as I was watching the Google Fiber announcement this morning. Whether or not Google realizes it, they’re winding up to uppercut the Dewey model of public school education in the chin.
Khan academy, Coursera, Udacity, MITx, and Stanford’s online offerings are all awesome initiatives in democratizing world class education online. Accredited universities like Southern New Hampshire have moved to facilitating entire degrees at a competitive price online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Get Banks Using FiSync</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/how-to-get-banks-using-fisync-92018a7ee8c9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/how-to-get-banks-using-fisync-92018a7ee8c9/</guid>
      <description>I’m going to write about Dwolla again because I really wouldn’t be too mad if Ben Milne and company decided to offer me a job. That, and I have the wonderful opportunity of interning at a community bank so I feel somewhat comfortable with the subject matter.
One of my tasks at this bank has involved researching new ATM technology and I can assure you those things are ridiculously expensive for the limited technology they provide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dwolla: Financial Trojan Horse</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/dwolla-financial-trojan-horse-8b7cb1170f21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/dwolla-financial-trojan-horse-8b7cb1170f21/</guid>
      <description>Since nobody reads my blog, aside from the 140 that read my cover letter yesterday (humble brag), I thought I’d pen something on Dwolla. Why Dwolla? Because their wonderfully kind CEO tweeted back at me last night. Don’t know what Dwolla is, Ashton Kutcher invested in it. I’m sure that’s all you needed to know so I’ll continue assuming you’ve stopped reading.
Dwolla is a Trojan horse; at least I hope it is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cover Letter I Wish I Could Send</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/the-cover-letter-i-wish-i-could-send-c23266944ecc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2012 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/the-cover-letter-i-wish-i-could-send-c23266944ecc/</guid>
      <description>Hey future employer,
How freaking tired of reading cover letters are you? I’m two sentences into writing one and I’m bored! Let’s just Skype over coffee from different Starbucks or maybe invite me over and we can reenact Chopped. You give me four ingredients, I’ll give you four, and the best meal wins. I’ll even give you an advantage and tell you your four ingredients ahead of time: brussels sprouts, black licorice, alligator and quinoa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android and ChromeOS Will Have a Baby</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/android-and-chromeos-will-have-a-baby-fdb309e0f42f/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/android-and-chromeos-will-have-a-baby-fdb309e0f42f/</guid>
      <description>Comments at D10 about the future merging of Android and ChromeOS have stirred up quite the speculation today. It seems like a natural path to me so I wrote about it.
Android is the technological step after the desktop. ChromeOS is the step after that, but arguably years away. How does Android grow up to one day become ChromeOS? By integrating cloud technologies into the OS so as to be hardware agnostic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If I Were Commissioner of the Big XII</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/if-i-were-commissioner-of-the-big-xii-fa8848c76599/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/if-i-were-commissioner-of-the-big-xii-fa8848c76599/</guid>
      <description>In a series of blog posts I may write in a day or over the course of months, depending on my motivation, I will lay out steps I think should be taken to strengthen the faltering BCS conference. As a former football player for the University of Kansas I have a vested interest in seeing the conference succeed and become a leader in college athletics.
It should be duly noted that college athletics is in the entertainment business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Culture and College Athletics</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/corporate-culture-and-college-athletics-dceec66fed04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/corporate-culture-and-college-athletics-dceec66fed04/</guid>
      <description>I think I’ll probably come back to this subject many times but I thought I’d blog about something serious. College athletics is a professional venture. It’s an odd entity funded by public universities, private donations and ticket sales. In return for getting state money it puts on a veil of equality and parity between football, basketball and non revenue sports. While I don’t have inside information on every athletics department in the country I imagine the mentality is very much about maximizing revenues in football and basketball and reducing expenditures in other sports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>@Twitter TV</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/twitter-tv-7e2ceedb4778/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/twitter-tv-7e2ceedb4778/</guid>
      <description>Cable providers are dead; the same way RIM is dead. I think Twitter is positioned to be a driving force behind the content revolution in creation and consumption. Yes, Twitter insists it’s not a media company but they’re wrong. Twitter could be the procurer of big data for media creators whether it’s music, books or television. Hold your tongue before you start babbling about Facebook.
Dick Costello just gave a presentation about Twitter this week; I didn’t watch but I did read headlines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Netflix</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/beyond-netflix-cc6908364b1c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/beyond-netflix-cc6908364b1c/</guid>
      <description>I am cleaning out my room; I have far too much stuff. If I ever want to move without having to contemplate burning everything, there’s a lot of stuff that needs to go.
One of these things is my DVD collection (of which I’ve added nothing new to in at least 3 years). The thing is, even though I don’t watch them, I own them and spent money on them and they take up a lot of space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Music Should Be Sold</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/how-music-should-be-sold-147619dc149f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/how-music-should-be-sold-147619dc149f/</guid>
      <description>Commercial artists make about $0.09 per track sold on iTunes or Amazon or so I read on various other blogs. I’ll be honest, I’ve never paid for a track on iTunes, I prefer streaming or using YouTube. I think music is overpriced, by a lot. How much would I be willing to pay for Watch the Throne? Approximately $0. How much would I pay to see the concert? Well, I was more than happy to spend $60; it was well worth it and I’m not a huge rap fan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If I Were Steve Balmer</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/if-i-were-steve-balmer-ab85db5f14a6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/if-i-were-steve-balmer-ab85db5f14a6/</guid>
      <description>I’d stop being an overpaid troll, get out of the hardware business and make Xbox live the new basis of my business.
Imagine a world where Xbox was open source and on TVs and PCs and pretty much everything not phones (you’d need a different version for phones) AND run it like Steam or OnLive. Everything had Kinect and Surface built in, content was delivered via the cloud personal or professional, Microsoft would have an identity system and social network, and your UI and UX wouldn’t look like hell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Google Music Is Better Than Great</title>
      <link>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/why-google-music-is-better-than-great-1f2444970108/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alpharoast.com/blog/bbthorson/why-google-music-is-better-than-great-1f2444970108/</guid>
      <description>Google’s done a lot lately that is out of touch with not being evil but at its core Google is still intent on breaking down silos (as long as its not their ad network) and giving motivated people the power to fight back.
Okay, that’s a little too utopian but I’ve hardly read about Google Music’s Artist Hub. Is it a new idea? Well I feel like most anybody could get their podcast or music on iTunes so no.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>